http://www.girlscoutsfl.org/en/our-council/privacy-policy.html

MY GS
ABOUT EVENTS VOLUNTEER COOKIES+ CAMPS+ OUR COUNCILAbout GSTFCouncil HistoryBoard Of DirectorsShare Your StoryHours & LocationsContact UsCareersOur BlogGSTF In The NewsGSTF Influencer Team SUPPORT US MY GS
Join
Donate
Shop
Contact Us
All Things GS
GS Help
About GSTFCouncil HistoryBoard Of DirectorsShare Your StoryHours & LocationsContact UsCareersOur BlogGSTF In The NewsGSTF Influencer Team
Our CouncilPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This website is owned by Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida, a 501(c)(3)
nonprofit organization.  [Our online properties comprise of, but are
not limited to, all pages found under www.girlscoutsfl.org. This
privacy policy applies to these sites and other sites, mobile apps or
other online services we operate that link to this policy
(collectively, referred to below as the site).]
Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida is committed to respecting and
protecting the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy discloses
how we collect, protect, and use information you provide or we collect
online, as well as how we protect children's privacy. If our policy
practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting our
revised privacy policy on our Web site. By using the pages on this
site or other services covered by the posted Privacy Policy, you are
accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION Personally Identifiable
Information. At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable
information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily
and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide
information to us in order to view our site. Girl Scouts of Tropical
Florida only gathers personally identifiable data on our site, such as
names, addresses, ZIP/postal codes, email addresses, etc., when
voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Once collected, we may combine
this information with other information collected from external sources.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Girl Scouts of Tropical
Florida may automatically collect certain technical information from
your computer such as your Internet service provider, your Internet
Protocol address, your browser type, your operating system, the pages
viewed, the pages viewed immediately before and after accessing the
Web site, and the search terms entered to get to our site. This
information allows us to improve and customize our services. We and
our service providers may collect this information using “cookies,”
which are small text files that many websites save on your computer,
or similar technologies. See the section on “Use of Cookies and
Similar Technology” below for more information.
USE AND SHARING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The personally identifiable information you provide is used by
Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida and other entities who are involved in
the operation of this site or who provide support for the Girl Scouts
of Tropical Florida and Girl Scouts of the USA mission and programs,
for general business purposes and for the purposes for which you
provided the information. General business purposes include, for
example, Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida and Girl Scouts of the USA
membership activities, program participation, marketing, promotions,
and fundraising activities and communications.  The purposes for which
you provide information includes our use of your personally
identifiable information to process online transactions, purchases,
and donations, facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and
Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida programs, promotions and services, or
process job applications. We do not sell information you provide to us
online with third parties. We may share personally identifiable
information with third parties including: (i) with other Girl Scout
Councils and Girl Scout troops for administrative purposes relating to
a child’s activities with another Council or their troop; (ii) when
the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it; (iii)
when sharing the information is with a service provider in furtherance
of our operations or the operation of the site, for instance, to
process a purchase or other transaction you make; (iv) to facilitate
participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl Scouts of Tropical
Florida programs, promotions, and services, or to engage in fund
raising, marketing communications and promotions; (v) to comply with
legal processes such as a subpoena or court order or to otherwise
protect your or our legal rights; or (vi) for other purposes for which
you provided the information. Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida has no
control over or responsibility for the data collection and use
practices of third parties that process online transactions. For
example, if you make a purchase on our site using a PayPal account or
similar account of a third party payment provider, certain information
is transmitted to the payment provider and is subject to the third
party’s own privacy policy.
Please note that Girl Scouts of the USA provides operational support
for the site and may collect and use personally identifiable
information you provide to the site and other information collected by
the site as described in this policy. Girl Scouts of the USA will use
any information it collects for the purposes described in this policy
and in a manner consistent with its own privacy policy, which is
available here. Girl
Scouts of Tropical Florida and Girl Scouts of the USA are each
responsible for their own information handling practices.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida is
committed to providing a safe, secure and fun online experience for
children who visit our site. We are dedicated to safeguarding any
personally identifiable information collected online and to helping
parents and children have positive experiences on the Internet.
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information
from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental
consent. With parental consent, we may collect information from
children under the age of 13 such as: name, address, email address,
account information, and user generated content. This information
allows us to fulfill a requested transaction and facilitate
participation in online programs, keep records, undertake certain
marketing activities or to otherwise customize or enhance the website
experience for children.
Children under the age of 13 may be able to make certain content
such as user generated content visible to others or the public. This
could include, for example, a webpage or parts of webpages operated by
children that have been designed for group or public viewing. However,
absent parental consent, children under 13 would be allowed to display
only limited information such as a first name or unique user name or
other information that does not allow for online contacting by third parties.
Regardless of what information is displayed, parents can revoke
their consent and ask that information about their children be deleted
from the site by contacting our offices by phone at 305-253-4841. To
do this or to review personally identifiable information collected
from children, we must verify the identity of the requesting parent.
When a parent revokes consent, we will stop collecting, using, or
disclosing information from that child. To respect the privacy of
parents, information collected and used for the sole purpose of
obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing notice is not
maintained in retrievable form by the site if parental consent is not
obtained after a reasonable time.
Submissions Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida welcomes
children to learn more about our organization and, where appropriate,
participate in polls and surveys, as well as submit comments, artwork,
writings and other submissions for posting on our website. For this
reason, Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida follows the guidelines for
interactive electronic media published by the Children's Advertising
Review Unit (CARU) of the Better Business Bureau for pages targeted to
children under 13. However, we encourage this be done only with their
parent's knowledge and supervision. We also encourage children to use
an alias (e.g., "Bookworm", "Skater", etc.), first
name, nickname, initials or other alternative to full names or screen
names which correspond with an email address for any activities which
will involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of email
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES Visitors should
be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically
collected by the Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida website through the
use of "cookies" or other similar technologies such as web
beacons. "Cookies" are small text files a website can use to
recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to
and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and
compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies
are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files.
Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor
that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not
want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a
simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or
accept the cookie feature. “Web beacons” are a small snippet of code
embedded in webpages typically used to monitor activity on a webpage
and transfer or collect information, such as information about your
Internet Protocol address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is
located, the browser type that is accessing the site, and the ID
number of cookies placed on your computer.
Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida uses "cookie" technology
only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors in
order to improve visitors' online experience and facilitate their
visit within our site. Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida may use web
beacons to improve website services, conduct website analytics, first
party advertising relating to us and our sponsors and to optimize the
browsing experience.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our website. These companies may use non-personally
identifiable information (that is, not including your name, address,
email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other
websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services
of interest to you on this or other websites. Read more information
about this
practice at http://www.networkadvertising.org
and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICES This site may be
linked to other sites and services that are not maintained by Girl
Scouts of Tropical Florida. These websites have their own privacy
policies, which you should review prior to visiting them. We have no
responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for
the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD The safety and security of your
online experience is of the utmost concern to us. We take measures to
implement reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to
safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security
and correctly use the information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety Protecting the safety of your credit
card information is also important to us. For card transactions we
process, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the
security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us.
SSL is an Internet encryption technology and a method of scrambling
data as it travels from your computer to our website servers. We also
encrypt your credit card number when we store your order and whenever
we transfer that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
sensitive information, check the document for your browser for
indication of an SSL connection (most browsers utilize an unbroken or
closed padlock). Verify that SSL is active before submitting sensitive
information to our server. To double-check, verify that the URL or
Address line of your browser for our site begins with "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian
permission to use a credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US If you have any questions about our
Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Girl Scouts of Tropical Florida 11347 SW 160th
Street Miami, FL  33157 Phone:  305-253-4841
Monday-Friday, 9:00 a.m. to 5 p.m.
Thank you for visiting our site.
This Privacy Policy was last updated 11/23/2016.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
